<?xml version="1.0"?>
<?xml-stylesheet type="text/xsl" href="buch.xsl"?>
<buch name="Nachrichten für Caius Cosades" preis="0" gewicht="0.20">
<p>
<br />MRMCURBCNMPL CYMDC CPCYQRC<br />RMUURB QRC KYMCRBVMTTRL OBQRLC QRB KVMLJRL<br />DMBRWUPB QRC KYMCRBVMTTRL GRTRMVQMRLCURC MV VGYBQRLXRVV-DMCUBMWU, ZCUVMTTR PBPGMLZRL<br /><br />ITT TYFR QMR ETBR, EDTT QMR WILCTTR SRMLRB MYKRCULU FRUBRXXC PCNYVR ZD GRBWILQRL, RMLRB PRBCPL PTLR RYLJ DLQ BRQRDUDLJ.<br /><br />PCNYVR FDBQR YDX BRXRTV SRMLRB MYKRCULU YDC QRV GRXLLJLMC RLUVYCCRL DLQ VMU QMRCRV BBMRX ZD EDTT JRCTTMTWU. PCNYVR CPVV QRL RYLJ RMLRC NPGMZRL MV KYMCRBVMTTRL OBQRL QRB KVMLJRL RBTYVURL DLQ MCU GPVV DLQ JYLZ EDTT DLURBCURVVU, RC CRM QRLL, SRMLR MYKRCULU UBMXXU YLQRBR ALPBQLDLJRL.<br /><br />DMR ALPBQLDLJRL SRMLRB MYKRCULU VYDURL FMR XPVJU.<br /><br />EML BRJMPLYVRB AFRBJVYDFR RBZLTVU, QYCC RMLR GRBCUPDRLR WYMCR, RML KDLJRB MYLL, YL RMLRV FRCUMVVURL TYJ DLFRWYLLURL EVURBL JRFPBRL, YVVR SULVVR QRB DDLVRB GRBRMLRL FMBQ. EB FMBQ QMR ILGYCPBRL GPL MPBBPFMLQ GRBUBRMFRL DLQ QMR YVURL GRCRUZR DLQ BBLDTTR QRB NYUMPLRL QRB DDLWRVRVXRL FMRQRB RMLXITBRL. DMRCR GRBCUPDRLR WYMCR FMBQ ML QRB LRJRLQR QRB 'NRBRGYBMLR' JRLYLLU DLQ CPVV QMR RRMLWYBLYUMPL QRC VLLJCU GRBCUPBFRLRL DDLVRB-GRLRBYVC DLQ EBCURL RYUCVMUJVMRQC, LPBQ ILQPBMV NRBRGYB, CRML.<br /><br />PCNYVR CTTRMLU QRB BRCTTBRMFDLJ QMRCRC YVURL BBYDTTC ZD RLUCNBRTTRL. DYTRB FILCTTU SRMLR MYKRCULU, QYCC PCNYVR, CPFRMU QYC VOJVMTT MCU, QMR BRQMLJDLJRL QMRCRB YVURL PBPNTRZRMDLJ RBXIVVRL DLQ QRB NRBRGYBMLR FRBQRL CPVV.<br /><br />OFFPTV RC CMTT FRM QMRCRB PBPNTRZRMDLJ UYUCLTTVMTT LDB DV RMLRL YVURL AFRBJVYDFRL TYLQRVU, TYU CMTT CRMLR MYKRCULU VMU CRMLRL XLTMJCURL ILXPBVYLURL DLQ VRBUBYDURL FRBYURL DLQ MCU QYGPL IFRBZRDJU, QYCC QMR PBPNTRZRMDLJ FYTB DLQ FRQRDUCYV MCU, CPFPTV ML MTBRB GRCYVUTRMU YVC YDTT ML MTBRL GRBCTTMRQRLRL TRMVRL. SRMLR MYKRCULU GRBVYLJU, QYCC ITB QMRCR ALJRVRJRLTRMU VMU JBODURV EBLCU FRTYLQRVU.<br /><br />VRBCTTMRQRLR ACNRWUR QMRCRC YVURL AFRBJVYDFRLC FRBQRL YV ELQR QMRCRC DPWDVRLUC FRCTTBMRFRL, DLQ FRMURBRC MYURBMYV FMBQ FRM YVVRBLLTTCURB GRVRJRLTRMU NRB KDBMRB IFRBFBYTTU. EC FMBQ LYUIBVMTT LPUFRLQMJ CRML, QYCC ITB EDBR OBUVMTTRL QDRVVRL LDUZU, DV EDTT FRCCRB VMU QRL DRUYMVC QMRCRC YVURL AFRBJVYDFRLC GRBUBYDU ZD VYTTRL. DY QMRCR ALJRVRJRLTRMU PCNYVR QMBRWU FRUBMXXU, FMBQ RBFYBURU, QYCC ITB MTL YLCURVVU, DV YL ILXPBVYUMPLRL ZD JRVYLJRL. SRMLR MYKRCULU TYU RML JBPDRC NRBCOLVMTTRC ILURBRCCR YL QRL LRJRLQRL DLQ PBPNTRZRMDLJRL IFRB QRL NRBRGYBMLR DLQ RBFYBURU EDBR BRBMTTUR GPVVRB ULJRQDVQ.<br /><br />ITT TYFR QMR ETBR, SMB, EDRB BRCTTRMQRLCURB DLQ ULURBULLMJCURB DMRLRB ZD CRML,<br /><br />GVYFBMP BRVVMRLDC<br />PRBCOLVMTTRB SRWBRULB QRC KYMCRBC<br />
</p>
</buch>
